A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Photographic Files, RG 4 FA1288
Rockefeller Archive Center
Institute of International Education records, Photographic Files, RG 4
1920-2006
Rockefeller Archive Center
Institute of International Education (New York, N.Y.)
FA1288
27.7 Cubic Feet 68 letter-size document boxes, 2 legal-size document boxes, 1 half-legal box, and 1 tall document box.
Scope and Contents
Contains photos, slides, still images, and associated correspondence or memoranda documenting conferences, workshops, annual reports, people, balls, galas, and other events as well a limited volume of biographical files and alumni profiles.
Arrangement
Series designated by Accession. Files are loosely alphabetically arranged.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Institute of International Education archives were deposited at the RAC by IIE in June 2016. Records were transferred to RAC by the Institute of International Education through several accessions in 2017.
Related Materials
The Council for International Exchange of Scholars (CIES) collection is available at the University of Arkansas.
The Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars records are available at the New York Public Library.
The International Fellowship Fund (IFF) Archives are available at Columbia University.
Biographical / Historical
The Institute of International Education (IIE) was established in 1919 by Nobel Prize winners Nicholas Murray Butler, Elihu Root and Stephen Duggan, Sr. The founders sought greater understanding among nations, primarily through the establishment of international educational exchange between United States institutes of higher education and foreign actors interested in formulating and developing active and ongoing educational understanding. As the Institute grew, developed and matured, it has continued to focus in the area of scholars exchange, as well as education services, international development and leadership training.
IIE initially focused on facilitating student, faculty, and teacher exchanges with European countries. In the 1930s their scope expanded beyond Europe to include exchanges between the Soviet Union and Latin America. During this period the Institute also established the Emergency Committee to Aid Displaced German Scholars which later expanded to include scholars fleeing facist Spain and Italy as well. In the 1950s this program was utilized to support Hungarian refugees. In the early 2000s IIE Trustees together with other donors endowed the Scholar Rescue Fund (SRF).
Following WWII, the Institute helped establish the Association of International Educators (NAFSA) and the Council on International Education Exchange (CIEE) for which they serve to administer the CIEE faculty component and the graduate student component of the Fullbright program, which continues to today as the Institute's largest program.
Other Finding Aids
Institute of International Education records are available in the following other finding aids:
Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 (FA1289)
Institute of International Education records, Fellowship Cards (Grantee Locator Cards), RG 2(FA1290)
Institute of International Education records, Publications, Paper records, RG 3, Series 1 (FA1291)
Institute of International Education records, Publications, Microfoms, RG 3, Series 2 (FA1315)
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Photographs
- Photographic Files, Accession 2016:070, 1920-2006; 1
  - Artes Liberates Conference in Budapest, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Art Conference, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asia (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biennial, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Beth Moore Luncheon, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bok, Derek (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting and Hollabd Awardees Reception, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Annual Report Photo Slides, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report-Midwest, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report-Midwest, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report-Rocky Mountain, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report-South, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports-South, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports-West Coast, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports-West Coast, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Goodman (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Adelman, Alan (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural Institutions (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Africa and African Students (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Albany State College (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Albright, Madeline (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - American Students Abroad (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - American Teachers Abroad (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Amoco Azerbaijan, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Anderson, Dorothy (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - International Students, 1950s (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Historical Files (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Delaware Foreign Study Plan, 1920s (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - History of IIE Overseas Offices (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, Artes Liberales (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - IIE History (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Diamond Ball 1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Diamond Ball 1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Distinguished Alumni (Box 5, Folder 39-40)
  - Diamond Ball - 3rd Global Gala 1962 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Distinguished People (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Diamond Ball - Global Gala 4th - 1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Diamond Ball 1975, Digital material within (Box 6, Folder 44-46)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made please contact an archivist.
  - Diamond Ball 1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Cornell University (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Corporate Dinner 1971 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Corporate Dinner 1976 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Corporate Dinner 1979 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Corporate Luncheon 1982 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Creole Award to IIE (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Cutler, Dr. Howard A. (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Czech Republic - Ministry of Health and Social Welfare (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Dearborne Assembly; Ford Motor Co., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - DePaul University (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Carter, James E. (Jimmy) (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - CEEB Workshop, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Cherrington, Ben (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - CHEAR Conference 1968 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Chicago Annual Benefit 1988 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Chicago Fulbright Seminars 1987 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Chicago-Northwestern Traveling Seminar, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - China, American Study Info. Center (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 1989 - China Foundation Gathering (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - CHS Luncheon on the Arts, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Columbia University (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Convocation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 69-72)
  - Annual Report 1995 IIE (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Annual Report, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Arts (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Art Show, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Boston University (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Brigham Young University (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - British Festivals-Princess Anne, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Bush, George Sr. (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - California State Polytechnic College (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Cannon, Dolly (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Fulbrighters (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Diamond Ball, 1974; Digital material within (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Diamond Ball, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Foreign Student Parties, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - Miscellaneous Foreign Universities (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Former IIE Presidents (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Former IIE Staff Members (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Former IIE Trustees (Box 11, Folder 90-91)
  - Former IIE Vice Presidents (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - France (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Freedom Support Act, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Friendly Fellowships, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Fulbright 40th Dinner, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Fulbright Artists Exhibit, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Fulbright Design Show, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - E.A. Seminar, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - E.A. Overseas Trip to Southeast Asia, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 100-101)
  - Edgerton, Wallace (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - East Timor Educational Exchange Project, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Egypt (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Cairo, Egypt, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Empress of Iran's Visit to IIE, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Foreign Exchange Student Farewell, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Foreign Fulbright Student Conference, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Foreign Students Reception, 1950s (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Duggan, Stephen and Lawrence (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Asia-Pacific Women in the Non Governmental Sector (WINGS) and RAMP - Mexico founding meeting (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Foreign Students (Box 14, Folder 113-114)
  - E.A. Seminar, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - E.A. Seminar, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - E.A. Seminar, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Contact Sheets/Photos from 75th Anniversary Events: Kickoff, Washington, DC State Dept. Reception, Forum, Gala (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Contact Sheets/Photos from 75th Anniversary Events: Kickoff, Washington, DC State Dept. Reception, Forum, Gala (Box 15, Folder 119-123)
  - ITT Alumni Dinner, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - ITT Fellowships (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Japan - 40th Anniversary of Fulbright Program (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Japan - U.S. Women Leaders, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Jerzy Kosinski, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Joe Fowler Tribute, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Kansas State University (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Kaufmann International Design Award Presentation, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Anne Armstron, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Eliot Richardson, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Hodding Carter III, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Arnaud de Borchgrave, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Jeane Kirkpatrick, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Michael Swern, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Herbert Schmertz, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Zbigniew Brzezinski, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Porfirio Munoz-Ledo, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Paul Volcker (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Frank Stanton, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - William E. Simon, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Frank Hodsoll, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Dr. Helen Caldicott, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - David Owen, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - John J. McCloy, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 147)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Zhao Jinglun, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Franklin Murphy, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - McGeorge Bundy, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Sol Linowitz, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Hanna Holborn Gray, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Marshall Goldman, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Selwa Roosevelt, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Arthur Schlesinger, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - DeMontebello, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 156)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - L. Paul Bremer III, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 157)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Mathilde Krim, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 158)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Tommy Koh, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 159)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - David Gergen, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - John Frohmayer, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Timothy Healy, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Jeanie Rosoff, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Lizabeth Settor (Box 19, Folder 164)
  - K. Holland Lecture Series - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 165)
  - Korwin International Music Competition, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - Krasno, Richard (Box 20, Folder 167)
  - Krasno, Richard & Kaufman, Henry (Box 20, Folder 168)
  - L.A. Crossroads, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  - La Voz de la OEA Conf. (Box 20, Folder 170)
  - Wingspread Conference, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 171)
  - Winter Party, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 172-173)
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 21, Folder 174)
  - USAID Caribbean Basin Initiatives Final Workshop, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 175)
  - USIA Orientation Seminar, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 176)
  - Venezuelan Program, 1974-1978 (Box 21, Folder 177)
  - Vietnamese Education Minister (Box 21, Folder 178)
  - Volunteers' Luncheon, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 179)
  - Volunteers' Recognition Ceremony, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 180)
  - Washington Board Council Meeting, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 181)
  - Washington University (Box 21, Folder 182)
  - Wayne State University (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - West German Educators Conference, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Western Reserve University (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Whitlock, Kenneth (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Wick, Charles (Box 21, Folder 187)
  - Wine Tasting, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 188)
  - Wine Tasting, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 189)
  - Wine Tasting, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 190)
  - Wine Tasting, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 191)
  - Wine Tasting, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - Winter Party, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 193-194)
  - Winter Party, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 195-196)
  - Winter Party, 1979; Some staining on the prints. (Box 23, Folder 197-200)
  - Winter Party, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - Winter Party, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 202)
  - Winter Party, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 203-204)
  - Winter Party, 1982; Some staining on back of prints; Emulsion worn on individual print (Box 24, Folder 205-208)
  - Ruth Gruber Book Signing, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 209-210)
  - South Africa Education Program, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 211)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) Conference, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 212)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) National Council Meeting, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 213)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) National Council Meeting, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 214)
  - South Africa, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 215)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) Conference, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 216)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) National Council Meeting, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 217)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 218)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - South Africa Education Program (SAEP) Conference, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 220)
  - Fulbright Scholar Program, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 221)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 222)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 26, Folder 223)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (Box 26, Folder 224)
  - U.S. Fulbright Fellows - Directories, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 225)
  - ECA SUNY - Meet USA Students, 1988 April (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Elizabeth [illegible] Moore, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 227)
  - United Nations Plaza and IIE Headquarters site (Box 27, Folder 228)
  - Becky (Box 27, Folder 229)
  - Documents on Latin America for Mr. Espinosa, Brittle pages (Box 27, Folder 230)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 1930s-1940s; Brittle pages (Box 28, Folder 231)
  - American Students Studying in Germany - Report Excerpts, 1933-1934 (Box 28, Folder 232)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 28, Folder 233)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (Box 28, Folder 234)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, 2002 March; Digital material within (Box 28, Folder 235)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 28, Folder 236-238)
  - Miscellaneous Photos (Box 29, Folder 239)
  - IIE Board of Trustees Meeting, 2001 January 22 (Box 29, Folder 240)
  - IIE Annual Reports, Digital material (Box 29, Folder 241)
  - Photo-Session 114 (Box 29, Folder 242-243)
  - IIE History and Alumni Program, 1963-1979 (Box 29, Folder 244)
  - IIE Staff, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 245)
  - International Visitor Program (Box 30, Folder 246)
  - Untitled Albums (Box 30, Folder 247-249)
  - Illinois Institute of Technology (Box 31, Folder 250)
  - Important Government Leaders Photos (Box 31, Folder 251)
  - Important Government Leaders Letters (Box 31, Folder 252)
  - India (Box 31, Folder 253)
  - Inter-American Conference, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 254)
  - IIE-RDF Awards, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 255)
  - IIE-RDF Awards, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 256)
  - IIE-RDF Awards, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 257)
  - IIE-RDF Awards, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 258-259)
  - IIE Jordan, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 260)
  - IIE Musical Artists (Box 32, Folder 261)
  - IIE Orientation Programs (Box 32, Folder 262)
  - IIE's President Meeting, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 263)
  - IIE-RDF Awards, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 264)
  - IIE-RDF Awards, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 265)
  - IIE - Lima Office (Box 33, Folder 266)
  - IIE - New York Office (Box 33, Folder 267)
  - IIE - Washington Office (Box 33, Folder 268)
  - IIE - Guandong (Box 33, Folder 269)
  - IIE - Hong Kong (Box 33, Folder 270)
  - IIE - Hong Kong Office Reception, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 271)
  - IIE - Houston Forum, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 272)
  - IIE - Information Center, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 273-274)
  - IIE - Atlanta Office (Box 33, Folder 275)
  - IIE - Art Program, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 276)
  - IIE - Bangkok Office (Box 34, Folder 277)
  - IIE - Chicago Office (Box 34, Folder 278)
  - IIE - Denver Office (Box 34, Folder 279)
  - IIE - Houston Office (Box 34, Folder 280)
  - ICEEO and FOCUS Premiere and Award Ceremony, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 281)
  - IIE - 50th Anniversary in Time Magazine, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 282)
  - Early IIE Photos, 1920s (Box 34, Folder 283)
  - Early IIE Photos, 1930s (Box 35, Folder 284-286)
  - Latin America (Box 35, Folder 287)
  - Louisiana State University (Box 35, Folder 288)
  - Launch of Asia Help, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 289)
  - Liberia (Box 35, Folder 290)
  - Lie, Trygve (Box 35, Folder 291)
  - Linowitz, Amb. Sol M. (Box 35, Folder 292)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (Box 35, Folder 293)
  - Luce Interns, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 294)
  - Macalester College (Box 35, Folder 295)
  - Mack, Tracy - GE3 Grantee (Box 35, Folder 296)
  - Manchester Program - Ford Motor Co., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 297)
  - Meeting between Reps. of USSR and IIE, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 298)
  - Mexican-American Journalists, 1993; Silver mirroring (Box 36, Folder 299)
  - Mexican-American Artists Project (Box 36, Folder 300)
  - Mexican-American Program - L.A. (Box 36, Folder 301)
  - Mexico, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 302)
  - Mexico City, 1980-1983; Some staining on back of prints (Box 36, Folder 303)
  - Masachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 36, Folder 304)
  - Midwest Regional Benefit Dinner, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 305)
  - Moscow, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 306)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 307)
  - Mundt, Karl (Box 36, Folder 308)
  - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 36, Folder 309)
  - Nairobi, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 310)
  - Ness Student Party, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 311)
  - Ness Student Party, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 312)
  - 1960s - New Building (Box 37, Folder 313)
  - New York University (Box 37, Folder 314)
  - Nigeria (Box 37, Folder 315)
  - Richard Nixon (Box 37, Folder 316)
  - Ohio State University (Box 37, Folder 317)
  - Okinawa Training Program (Box 37, Folder 318)
  - Oklahoma State University (Box 37, Folder 319)
  - One Evening in May Benefit, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 320)
  - Oxford University (Box 37, Folder 321)
  - Pakistan (Box 37, Folder 322)
  - PAKS III, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 323)
  - Pennsylvania State University (Box 38, Folder 324)
  - Percy, Sen. Charles H. (Box 38, Folder 325)
  - Personnel, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 326)
  - Personnel, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 327)
  - Personnel, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 328)
  - Philip Morris Luncheon, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 329)
  - Philip Morris Presentation, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 330)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 331)
  - Project City Streets Community Leaders, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 332)
  - Project City Streets Community Leaders, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 333)
  - Purdue University (Box 39, Folder 334)
  - Purcell, Pearl G. (Box 39, Folder 335)
  - Reader's Digest Foundation Awards, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 336)
  - Ricci Benefit, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 337)
  - Ricci Benefit, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 338)
  - Ron Trawbridge Visit, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 339)
  - Roosevelt University (Box 39, Folder 340)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 39, Folder 341)
  - Royal Academy of Dramatic Arts Auditions, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 342)
  - Rutgers University (Box 40, Folder 343)
  - Untitled Album - Events (Box 40, Folder 344-346)
  - Untitled Album - Events (Box 41, Folder 347-352)
  - Distinguished American and Foreign IIE Alumni (students), Lecturers, Debaters, and Specialists (Box 42, Folder 353)
  - Events (Box 42, Folder 354-356)
  - Art Educates the World Feb. 2002 International Event, 2002 February (Box 42, Folder 357-358)
  - Art Educates the World Feb. 2002 International Event, 2002 February (Box 42a, Folder 359-361)
  - 80th Anniversary Event, 1999 (Box 42a, Folder 362)
  - 80th Anniversary Event, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 363-367)
  - IIE Training Programs (Box 43a, Folder 368)
  - IIE Vietnam (Box 43a, Folder 369)
  - Int'l Directors Meeting, 1998 (Box 43a, Folder 370)
  - IPDC Fellowship UNESCO-TV, 1984 (Box 43a, Folder 371)
  - Iran (Point 4 Prog.) (Box 43a, Folder 372)
  - Italy, Venice (Box 43a, Folder 373)
  - ITT Fellows (Box 43a, Folder 374)
  - Nancy Reagan and Barbara Bush (Box 43a, Folder 375)
  - 1979 Conference - International Education: The Global Context, the U.S. Role (Box 44, Folder 376)
  - Trustee Handbook - Alumni Project: 1930s Alumni Responses (Box 44, Folder 377-378)
  - Trustee Handbook - Alumni Project Correspondence, 2001 July-2002 July (Box 44, Folder 379-380)
  - Trustee Handbook - Alumni Project Correspondence, 2002 August-2003 September (Box 44, Folder 381-382)
  - Foundation Proposal Record, 1980-1992 (Box 45, Folder 383)
  - Capital Campaign 01 (Box 45, Folder 384)
  - Art Educates the World - February 27, 2002 - Event Details, 2002 February 27; Digital material within (Box 45, Folder 385)
  - IMPACT Brochure (Box 45, Folder 386-387)
  - Sarai Sherman Art Books (4 books) - Bound Volumes
    Available in the RAC Library collection.
  - South African Information Exchange Working Paper, Numbers 23, 25, 26 (Box 45, Folder 388)
  - South African Information Exchange Working Paper, Numbers 28 and 30 (Box 46, Folder 389)
  - South African Information Exchange Working Paper, Numbers 32 and 33 (Box 46, Folder 390)
  - 80th Anniversary Benefit Dinner (Box 46, Folder 391)
  - IIE Awards Dinner, 2002 October 29 (Box 46, Folder 392)
  - IIE Gala Dinner, 2000 November 30 (Box 46, Folder 393)
  - IIE Events and History Publications (Box 46, Folder 394)
  - GMA (Box 47, Folder 395)